// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single

export const quiz = {
    topic: 'Marvel',
    level: 'Beginner',
    totalQuestions: 10,
    perQuestionScore: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          'What does S.H.I.E.L.D. stand for?',
        choices: ['Stones Hidden In Extraterrestrial Lands and Demographics', 
                'Space Human Investigation on Energy, Light and Deities.', 
                'Strategic Homeland Intervention, Enforcement and Logistics Division', 
                'Strategic Hero Intervention, Enforcement and Logistics Division'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Strategic Homeland Intervention, Enforcement and Logistics Division',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What type of vehicle did Thanos briefly use in the comic books and make a brief appearance in the Loki series?',
        choices: ['A tank with “Infinity” written on it', 
                'A helicopter with “Thanos” written on the side', 
                'A car with “perfectly balanced” on the side', 
                'A motorbike with “Titan” on the side'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'A helicopter with “Thanos” written on the side',
      },
      {
        question:
          'In which order are the Infinity Stones revealed in the Marvel Cinematic Universe?',
        choices: [
          'Time Stone, Space Stone, Power Stone, Soul Stone, Reality Stone and Mind Stone',
          ' Power Stone, Reality Stone, Time Stone, Space Stone, Mind Stone and Soul Stone',
          'Reality Stone, Time Stone, Mind Stone, Soul Stone, Power Stone and Space Stone',
          'Space Stone, Mind Stone, Reality Stone, Power Stone, Time Stone and Soul Stone',
        ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Space Stone, Mind Stone, Reality Stone, Power Stone, Time Stone and Soul Stone',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of the following items of Jewelry does Ben from Fantastic 4 try to pick up from the pavement?',
        choices: [
            'Ring',
            'Necklace',
            'Earring',
            'Bangle',
        ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Ring',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What was Steven Strange’s career before he learned to use magic?',
        choices: [
            'An Accountant',
            'A Lawyer',
            'A Surgeon',
            'An Astronaut',
        ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'A Surgeon',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What type of radiation gave Bruce Banner the ability to turn into the Hulk?',
        choices: [
            'Gamma',
            'Infrared',
            'Ultraviolet',
            'Microwave',
        ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Gamma',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What are the leaders of the TVA in the Loki Series called?',
        choices: [
          'Peacekeepers',
          'Gatekeepers',
          'Timekeepers',
          'Stonekeepers',
        ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Timekeepers',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What does Thanos want to bring to the universe?',
        choices: [
          'Hope',
          'Balance',
          'Destruction',
          'Peace',
        ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Balance',
      },
      {
        question:
          'In which movie does Stan Lee appear in a library with headphones on?',
        choices: [
          'Ant Man and the Wasp',
          'Thor: The Dark World',
          'Spiderman: Homecoming',
          'The Amazing Spiderman',
        ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'The Amazing Spiderman',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of the following characters did not disappear during the ”blip”?',
        choices: [
          'Nebula',
          'Spiderman',
          'Black Panther',
          'Groot',
        ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Nebula',
      },
    ],
  }